All standard deviations are called sampling.
Now, if I consider the feedback of all of them, I will make a product.
But beyond that, the product should be opinionated.
That's what I said. I don't know what to say.
That's what I said.
Literally...
I forgot the program.
I forgot it just now.
Just a month ago.
So I said, the best time I have seen startups,
don't do it because someone else wants it.
Don't do it because you want to do a startup.
Do it because you are frustrated enough
that no product exists to solve your problem.
I mean, yes, bro.
I was frustrated enough to do it for whom.
So, according to me, we want this.
What is the best bet, bro?
I have already told you. You can take the whole new tactic.
What are you doing?
Don't take the displacement.
You go through that process of formula.
Either we work on my opinion,
or you come with your opinions,
but we are not doing it for any customer.
Because this perfect sampling is impossible at this moment.
And we didn't even look for a sample.
We asked them, will you use it like this?
They said no.
That does not mean that this product will not exist in the future.
People cannot tell their problems.
I told you, what is your major problem?
You will be like...
I also said it in the last episode.
I don't understand this concept that people decide to do a startup
and then they think what to do.
It is simply that you are so interested in a project,
that it becomes a startup.
And recently...
You spoke about it.
It has been a month.
It all just reaffirms my...
It makes sense.
There is no difference between the two.
That's it.
These are the three best optimizations.
And this optimization is working for this pre-filled form.
So he will also understand.
He will say, this is the profile.
If this profile does like this, will it be like this?
He will put my profile.
I will put it.
I will never think that I should put the truth.
I will always think...
Who will look?
I will not put anything. Exactly.
I will think that I can do the best.
I don't want to put my current income.
I will say that my income will be this much in a year and a half.
I can do the best. I will not put it.
How can you show me like this?
I will say that I will put my current income.
Also, if you want to show that...
In the next section...
I want to do something.
Somewhere on this page...
Tool design.
Somewhere on this page, this form.
Three tool tips.
And at least two rows of tables.
If you see one...
At one glance, you will know how this page was made.
That's what I was saying.
You will know when you see it.
When the form is filled, you will get the tips.
And there is a table at the bottom to compare.
If you put it here, what can you do about it?
But the thing is...
If you put the first information...
You can't take all the pieces of the first information.
Yes, correct.
Once I put it there...
Automatically, based on this...
If you put it here...
Then it will look like this.
Suppose I put the income there.
Then I change the property value.
Then I change the age.
Then the monthly income will go down.
If you change by this...
ROI will change.
But before that, tell me what is the ROI?
Yes, correct.
So basically, Google sites don't have the same information.
If you put one information somewhere...
It means if you put all the information...
We don't know where it will come from.
Okay.
We need two tips.
Do you know what is API?
This one is API.
First time API is available.
Otherwise, this is all front-end only.
What do you have to listen?
Okay.
Coming down.
And just eligibility is not a good word.
Fine-tune...
Super-English rule.
Super-English, yes.
C option.
What is C option?
Okay.
Then what is this?
You are assuming that your existing exists.
It is written down.
Then this button is misleading.
This button is misleading.
I thought this button is not openable.
But there is a drop-down there.
Is there a drop-down there?
No, no, no.
So should I do a demo or a drop-down?
This is given in the C options line.
If you open it in the center...
No, there is no drop-down.
What kind of mistake is this?
What is the mistake?
No, there is a drop-down.
You can open a drop-down with this button.
But as far as C options are concerned...
Adjust eligibility...
and C options.
I don't know what options.
C options is not a good answer.
C banks.
Which means both of them are very different.
C options.
Submit.
But this is not...
Submit is like...
Submit is for form submits.
Yes, it is a form submit.
C options is definitely not the answer.
Form.
Just C options.
Just move it.
C options should be below this adjust eligibility.
Anyway, when you adjust eligibility...
there should be a button here.
If I adjust eligibility over here...
then I have to go to this button...
to see...
It should not come below this.
This button...
Additional parameters.
Adjust eligibility...
should become something else.
Like...
Additional columns.
Additional attributes.
Additional parameters.
But something in very simple English.
And this C options...
should be a button...
that is below this adjust eligibility.
And in center.
In the same...